

<u>İBRAHİM BAŞAR YARGICI</u>

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - STUDENT

I have been studying Computer Engineering for 3 years, and now working at ING. The tech stack that I have worked on before are Android, Flutter, Spring-Boot and Unity. Additionally, I am taking active roles in communities such as doing live streams and cohostings.



ibrahimbyargici@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/ibrahimbasaryargici

+90 543 386 2624

github.com/basarYargici



WORK EXPERIENCE

Android Developer - Part Time

ING (International Netherlands Group)

11/2021 - Present

Working on developing the new mobile application of ING using cutting edge libraries using MVVM with Clean Architecture.

- Multi-Repo Approach
- · Jetpack libraries such as HILT and Navigation component

Information Technologies Intern

Middle East Technical University 08/2021 - 09/2021

Worked on finding and adapting the most compatible and robust monitoring software to the system to monitor the agents.

- On Linux OS, Multi Router Traffic Grapher and CACTI softwares are containerized on Docker to run over servers.
- · Tools: Docker, MRTG

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Flutter Hackathon 2021

Deeplearning.ai 02/2021

Al For Everyone

Deeplearning.ai 12/2020

Crash Course on Python

Google 12/2020

Introduction to Programming With Java

BTK Academy 05/2020 - 08/2020

Android Mobile Application Development with Kotlin Basic Level And Advanced Level

BTK Academy 05/2020 - 08/2020

Introduction to Digital Game Development with Unity

BTK Academy 05/2020 - 08/2020

Educational Games with Unity

BTK Academy 05/2020 - 08/2020

ML Days Study Jam

Deep Learning Turkey – Global AI Hub 05/2020

Facebook DEVC Ideathon Certificate

Facebook 01/2020

English Preparatory Program Certificate

Istanbul Arel University 05/2019

SKILLS

Java Android Kotlin

Spring-Boot

Flutter

С

SQL

PostgreSQL

Git

EDUCATION

BS. Computer Engineering

Istanbul University 2021-...

BS. Computer Engineering

Istanbul Arel University (Full Tuition Scholarship, CGPA = 3.92 / 4.00) 2018-2021 Istanbul

High School

Nişantaşı High School (84.89/100) 2013-2017 Istanbul

ACHIEVEMENTS

Core Team Member

I do live streams and sharing my knowledge on software development topics with **FolksDev** brand.

Core Team Member

I am involved in **Turkey Java Community** as a core team member who aims to share know-how between Java users, to improve Java usage and to expand Java user network.

LANGUAGES

English

Professional working proficiency

Turkish

Native or bilingual proficiency